Guide to the Paula Green papers, 1940-2013 and undated RL.11500
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1959-2013 and undated; 6
  - 720. New York Times, Undated (Box AV15, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-199)
    Fashions of the Times :30
  - 722. New York Times, Undated (Box AV15, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-200)
    7 commercials
  - 724. New York Times, Undated (Box AV15, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-201)
  - 724. New York Times, Undated (Box AV15, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-202)
    Conductor Home Delivery :10; Tammy Grimes :30
  - 725. New York Times, 1975 (Box AV15, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-203)
  - 726. New York Times, Undated (Box AV15, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-204)
    Pearl Bailey :30
  - 727. New York Times, 1974 (Box AV15, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-205)
    12 commercials
  - 728. New York Times, Undated (Box AV15, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-206)
  - 729. New York Times, Undated (Box AV15, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-207)
    Ragtime :30 Max Morath
  - 730. New York Times, 1975 (Box AV15, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-208)
    Arts and Leisure Lauren Bacall
  - 800. Sun show reel 12:30, Undated (Box AV15, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-209)
  - 802. New York Post, 1977 (Box AV15, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-210)
    Oil Sheiks :30
  - 803. New York Post, Undated (Box AV16, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-211)
    Tape 5 auditions: Yolanda Childress; Marvin Lichterman; Vicky Rauch; Bill Griffis
  - 804. New York Post, Undated (Box AV16, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-212)
    Total Joy :30
  - 804. New York Post, Undated (Box AV16, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-213)
  - 807. Marval Turkeys, 1979 (Box AV16, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-214)
    Breakaway :30; Charts :30; Elegant Table :30
  - 814. Marval Poultry, 1979 (Box AV16, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-215)
    Now's the Time :30
  - 818. Marval Poultry, 1982 (Box AV16, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-216)
    I Do, I Do :10; Pledge :10; Parts :10
  - 818. Marval Poultry, 1982 (Box AV16, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-217)
  - 821. Marval Poultry, Undated (Box AV16, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-218)
    Summertime Turkey
  - 821. Marval Poultry, Undated (Box AV16, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-219)
  - 822. Marval Poultry, 1982 (Box AV16, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-220)
    Turkeys
  - 900. Jacomo "Together", 1977 (Box AV16, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-221)
  - 901. Jacomo "Together", 1977 (Box AV16, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-222)
  - 902. Goya Foods, Undated (Box AV16, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-223)
    Bean Table :30; Pink Beans :30; Black Bean Soup :30
  - 903. Goya Foods, 1979 (Box AV16, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-224)
    Toni Ficalora complete shoot
  - 904. Goya Foods, 1979 (Box AV17, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-225)
  - 906. Goya Foods, 1983 (Box AV17, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-226)
    Bean Book :30
  - 906. Goya Foods, 1983 (Box AV17, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-227)
  - 910. Goya Foods, 1980 (Box AV17, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-228)
    Hermione #1 takes 1-52
  - 913. Goya Foods, 1983 (Box AV17, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-229)
    Healthy Eating :30; Salad Toss :30; Add 'Ems :30
  - 913. Goya Foods, 1983 (Box AV17, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-230)
  - 913. Goya Foods, Undated (Box AV17, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-231)
    Goya Beans with Zohra Lampert
  - 914. Goya Foods, 1983 (Box AV17, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-232)
    Lazy Susan logos
  - 915. Goya Foods, 1984 (Box AV17, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-233)
    Cass I takes 1-55
  - 918. Goya Foods, 1983 (Box AV17, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-234)
    Reel 1-A takes 1-16
  - 919. Goya Foods, 1983 (Box AV17, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-235)
    Reel 1 takes 17-101
  - 920. Goya Foods, 1983 (Box AV17, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-236)
    Reel 2
  - 921. Goya Foods, 1983 (Box AV17, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-237)
    Reel 3
  - 922. Goya Foods, 1983 (Box AV17, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-238)
    Reel 3 production material
  - 923. Goya Foods, 1983 (Box AV18, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-239)
    Reel 4
  - 924. Goya Foods, 1983 (Box AV18, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-240)
    Reel 5 60:00
  - 925. Goya Foods, 1983 (Box AV18, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-241)
    Reel 6
  - 926. Goya Foods, 1983 (Box AV18, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-242)
    Reel 7
  - 927. Goya Foods, 1983 (Box AV18, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-243)
    Reel 8
  - 928. Goya Foods, 1985 (Box AV18, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-244)
  - 929A. Goya Foods, 1985 (Box AV18, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-245)
    Reel 1 production material
  - 929B. Goya Foods, 1985 (Box AV18, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-246)
    Reel 2 production material
  - 930A. Goya Foods, 1985 (Box AV18, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-247)
    Playback Goya Sazon
  - 930B. Goya Foods, 1985 (Box AV18, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-248)
    Sazon dub
  - 930C. Goya Foods, 1985 (Box AV18, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-249)
    Sazon all takes
  - 931. Goya Foods, 1985 (Box AV18, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-250)
    Sazon Goya rough cut
  - 933. Goya Foods, 1985 (Box AV18, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-251)
    New Beans :30
  - 933. Goya Foods, 1985 (Box AV18, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-252)
  - 933. Goya Foods, 1985 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-253)
  - 934. Goya Foods, 1985 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-254)
    New Beans 3 spots; Sazon :30
  - 935. Goya Foods, 1987 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-255)
    Sazon :30
  - 935. Goya Foods, 1985 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-256)
  - 935. Goya Foods, 1985 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-257)
  - 935D. Goya Foods, 1987 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-258)
  - 935D. Goya Foods, 1987 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-259)
  - 935D. Goya Foods, 1987 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-260)
  - 935D. Goya Foods, 1987 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-261)
  - 935D. Goya Foods, 1987 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-262)
  - 935D. Goya Foods, 1987 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-263)
  - 936. Goya Foods, 1985 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-264)
    Sazon :30; New Beans :30
  - 937. Goya Foods, 1986 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-265)
    Salad Toss :30; New Beans :30; Sazon :30; Healthy Eating :30; The Add 'Ems :30
  - 937. Goya Foods, 1986 (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-266)
  - 938. Goya Foods, 1986 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-267)
    Freeze 'Ems :30; Front Porch :30
  - 939. Goya Foods, 1986 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-268)
    Goya Nectars shoot reel 1
  - 939. Goya Foods, 1986 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-269)
    Goya Nectars shoot reel 2
  - 939. Goya Foods, 1986 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-270)
    Goya Nectars shoot reel 3
  - 939. Goya Foods, 1986 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-271)
    Goya Nectars shoot reel 5
  - 939. Goya Foods, 1986 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-272)
    Goya Nectars shoot reel 4
  - 940. Adobo Chicken, 1986 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-273)
    Adobo the Chicken :30
  - 942. Goya Foods, 1986 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-274)
    Front Porch :30; Freeze 'Ems :30; obsolete never to leave the house
  - 941. Goya Foods, 1986 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-275)
    Goya tape 2
  - 941. Goya Foods, 1986 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-276)
    Goya tape 1
  - 941. Goya Foods, 1986 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-277)
    Goya tape 3
  - 943. Goya Foods, 1986 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-278)
    Goya 50th anniversary 2nd revision 10:00
  - 944. Goya Foods, 1986 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-279)
    Goya 50th anniversary English version 10:00
  - 945. Goya Foods, 1988 (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-280)
    Sazon Goya tape 2, day 2-3
  - 945. Goya Foods, 1988 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-281)
    Sazon Goya tape 1, day 2
  - 945. Goya Foods, 1988 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-282)
    Sazon Goya tape 1B
  - 945. Goya Foods, 1988 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-283)
    Sazon Goya tape 2A
  - 947. Goya Foods, 1988 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-284)
    Sazon Ginnie :30; Sazon Maria :30
  - 947. Goya Foods, 1988 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-285)
  - 948. Goya Foods, 1988 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-286)
    Goya Beans Place on Your Plate :30
  - 948. Goya Foods, 1988 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-287)
  - 949. Goya Foods, 1988 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-288)
  - 949. Goya Foods, 1988 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-289)
  - 950. Goya Foods, 1988 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-290)
    Place on Your Plate :15 versions
  - 951. Goya Foods, 1988 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-291)
    Sazon Ginnie rough edits 4 versions
  - 952. Goya Foods, 1988 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-292)
    Sazon Ginnie :15; Place on Your Plate :15
  - 1001. Sterling Bank, 1981 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-293)
    Doors :30
  - 1001. Sterling Bank, 1981 (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-294)
  - 1002. Sterling Bank, 1981 (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-295)
  - 1004. Sterling Bank, 1981 (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-296)
  - 1005. Sterling Bank, 1981 (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-297)
    Remote production material reel 2
  - 1005. Sterling Bank, 1981 (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-298)
    Remote production material reel 1
  - American Pie 19:00 preview, Undated (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-299)
  - Atherton Company Showreel, 1998 (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-300)
  - Chinatown dupe, 1977 (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-301)
  - Composite Reel, Syracuse cassette 1, 1997 (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-302)
  - Composite Reel 2, Syracuse, ILGWU, 1997 (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-303)
  - Daytime/Nightime show 94; Jason Robards part II, 57:00, Undated (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-304)
  - Green Dolmatch 5th anniversary, Undated (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-305)
  - ILGWU wild footage shot at Neptune, N.J. at Roxanne factory reel 2, 1992 (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-306)
  - ILGWU wild footage shot at Neptune, N.J. at Roxanne factory reel 1, 1992 (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-307)
  - Paula Green 16mm film transfers, Undated (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-308)
  - Unite presentation reel 8:00, 1995 (Box AV22, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-309)
  - Special Presentation for Full Spectrum Farms, 1989 (Box AV42, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-310)
  - Presentation: Alouette 12:00, 1989 (Box AV42, Video-cassette RL11500-UMATIC-311)
  - 112. Union Label spoofs, 1977 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-001)
  - 393. ILGWU Report to Convention, 1986 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-002)
  - 427. ILGWU Tokyo presentation, 1988 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-003)
  - 434. ILGWU "On Stage", 1990 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-004)
  - 435. Atlantic City material, Undated (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-005)
  - 435. ILGWU "On Stage", 1990 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-006)
  - 436. Channel One union history piece, Undated (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-007)
  - 439A. ILGWU casting session, 1991 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-008)
  - 442. ILGWU "On Stage" II, 1991 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-009)
  - 443. ILGWU presentation to Union Label Committee, 1992 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-010)
  - 444. ILGWU presentation to Union Label Committee, 1992 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-011)
  - 446. ILGWU Making a Commercial reel 1, 1992 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-012)
  - 446. ILGWU Making a Commercial reel 2, 1992 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-013)
  - 446F. ILGWU wild footage shot in Neptune NJ reel 1, 1992 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-014)
  - 450. ILGWU "We Make Jobs", 1992 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-015)
  - 451. ILGWU "We Make Jobs", 1992 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-016)
  - 463A. ILGWU reel 1, Undated (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-017)
  - 463B. ILGWU reel 2, 1994 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-018)
  - 464. ILGWU rough cut, 1994 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-019)
  - 466. ILGWU "Health Care", 1994 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-020)
  - 640A. Subaru spots, Undated (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-021)
  - 648. WLR Foods presentation, Undated (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-022)
  - 912. One Day at a Time, Undated (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-023)
  - 930. Goya Sazon, 1985 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-024)
  - A Day in New York by Nora Glickman with Zohra Lampert, Undated (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-025)
  - Clive Challis interview, 2000 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-026)
  - Clive Challis interview, Undated (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-027)
  - Goya Sazon reel 1 46:00, 1988 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-028)
  - Goya Sazon reel 2 46:00, 1988 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-029)
  - Goya Foods reel, 1989 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-030)
  - ILGWU auditions, 1984 (Box AV23, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-031)
    Phyllis, Jeffra, Jean, Connie
  - ILGWU composit of television commercials 1976-1987, 19 spots (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-032)
  - ILGWU first cut tape B, Undated (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-033)
  - ILGWU first fine cut, Roxanne "We Make Jobs", 1992 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-034)
  - ILGWU Factory Shoot Roxanne, 1992 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-035)
  - ILGWU "Health Care" :30, 1994 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-036)
  - ILGWU "Health Care" :30, 1994 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-037)
  - ILGWU "Health Care" :30, 1994 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-038)
  - ILGWU Joel and Perry's Excellent shoot, Roxanne factory, 1992 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-039)
  - ILGWU "Lillian" :60, 1988 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-040)
  - ILGWU "Miss America", 1991 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-041)
  - ILGWU "Miss America" reels 1-4, 1990 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-042)
  - ILGWU "Miss America" factory shots, Undated (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-043)
  - ILGWU Neptune shoot reel 1, 1992 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-044)
  - ILGWU Neptune shoot reel 2, 1992 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-045)
  - ILGWU Neptune shoot reel 3, 1992 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-046)
  - ILGWU Neptune shoot reel 4, 1992 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-047)
  - ILGWU Neptune shoot reel 5, 1992 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-048)
  - ILGWU Neptune shoot reel 6, 1992 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-049)
  - ILGWU Neptune shoot reel 7, 1992 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-050)
  - ILGWU Norma Jean, 60 Minutes Dec. 11, Undated (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-051)
  - ILGWU Production material reel 1 60:00, 1988 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-052)
  - ILGWU Production material reel 2 60:00, 1988 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-053)
  - ILGWU Production material reel 3 60:00, 1988 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-054)
  - ILGWU reel 1,2,3 90:00, 1991 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-055)
  - ILGWU reel 8, 1992 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-056)
  - ILGWU Report to the Convention 26:00, 1980 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-057)
  - ILGWU Report to the Convention 26:00, 1980 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-058)
  - ILGWU Report to the Convention 1983, 1989 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-059)
  - ILGWU Report to the Convention 16:00, 1983 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-060)
  - ILGWU Report to the Convention 12:00, 1989 (Box AV24, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-061)
  - ILGWU rough cut "We Make Jobs", 1992 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-062)
  - ILGWU rough wFX, Undated (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-063)
  - ILGWU Round-up presentation, "20 Years of Look for the Union Label", 1995 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-064)
  - ILGWU Seminar, 1984 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-065)
  - ILGWU "Statue" :30, 1987 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-066)
  - ILGWU tape 5 30:00, 1991 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-067)
  - ILGWU tape 6 30:00, 1991 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-068)
  - ILGWU tape 7 30:00, 1991 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-069)
  - ILGWU wild footage shot in Neptune NJ at Roxanne Factory reel 1, 1992 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-070)
  - ILGWU wild footage shot in Neptune NJ at Roxanne Factory reel 2, 1992 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-071)
  - ILGWU wild footage shot in Neptune NJ at Roxanne Factory reel 2, 1992 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-072)
  - ILGWU WWOR-TV, Undated (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-073)
  - Paula Green interview with Tamee Gunnell, 1996 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-074)
  - Paula Green interview with Tamee Gunnell, 1996 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-075)
  - Paula Green interview with Tamee Gunnell, 1996 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-076)
  - Sterling Bancorp, Bloomberg Forum interview with CEO Louis Cappelli, 1995 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-077)
  - Subaru spots, Undated (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-078)
  - Syracuse composite reel 1, 1997 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-079)
  - Syracuse composite reel 1, 1997 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-080)
  - Syracuse ILGWU spots and parodies reel 2, 1997 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-081)
  - Syracuse ILGWU spots and parodies reel 2, 1997 (Box AV25, Video-cassette RL11500-VHS-082)
  - 145 Tenants' Meeting tape 1, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-001)
  - 145 Tenants' Meeting tape 2, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-002)
  - Ad-Beat, Undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-003)
  - Advertising segment, AWRT seminar, 1973 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-004)
  - Amy ukelele, Undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-005)
  - Cancer Control WTFM 6:35, 8:53, 1976 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-006)
  - Bank Leumi 89R01782, 1989 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-007)
  - Cardio-Fitness Center radio spots 2x:60, Undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-008)
  - Charlie Osgood Strange and Unusual Christmas Music, News Radio WCBS, 1981 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-009)
  - Dougherty, Paula Green and Goya, 1983 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-010)
  - Goya: Composit Coco Goya Mixers demo, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-011)
  - Goya: Coco Goya Island version, version A, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-012)
  - Goya: Coco Goya Island version, version A, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-013)
  - Goya: Coco Goya Mixers demo w/Announcer, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-014)
  - Goya: Coco Goya Mixers Island Version #673, Undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-015)
  - Goya: Coco Goya Mixers Island Version #673, Undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-016)
  - Goya: Coco Goya Mixers radio mix 1 :60, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-017)
  - Goya: Coco Goya Mixers radio mix 2 :60, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-018)
  - Goya: Coco Goya Mixers radio mix 4 :60, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-019)
  - Goya: Coco Goya Mixers radio music/vocals :60, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-020)
  - Goya: Coco Goya Mixers radio rough demo :60, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-021)
  - Goya: Coco Goya Mixers radio version A sped up to :58.5, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-022)
  - Goya: Coco Goya Mixers radio without announcer, Undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-023)
  - Goya: Coco Goya revised voice-over, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-024)
  - Goya: Coco Goya revised voice-over, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-025)
  - Goya: Coco Goya voice-overs: Vaneese Thomas, Paula Green, Undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-026)
  - Goya: Goya Beans 3x:30, 1979 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-027)
  - Goya: Mixers radio :60, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-028)
  - Goya: Sazon test A and C, Undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-029)
  - Goya: Sazon test B: Maria and Joan, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-030)
  - Goya: Sazon test: Maria and Joan, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-031)
  - Goya: Sazon test: Maria and Joan, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-032)
  - Goya: Sazon test: Maria and Joan, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-033)
  - Goya: Sazon test: Maria and Joan, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-034)
  - Goya: Sazon test: Maria and Joan, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-035)
  - Goya: Sazon test: Maria and Joan, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-036)
  - Goya: Sazon test B: Maria and Joan, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-037)
  - Goya: Sazon test B: Maria and Joan, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-038)
  - Goya: Sazon test B: Maria and Joan, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-039)
  - Goya: Sazon test B: Maria and Joan, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-040)
  - Goya: Sazon test B: Maria and Joan, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-041)
  - Goya: Sazon test B: Maria and Joan, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-042)
  - Goya: Sazon test, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-043)
    Maria and Joan version A and B; Mom's Reward
  - Goya: Sazon test C: Mom's Reward, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-044)
  - Goya: Sazon test C: Mom's Reward, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-045)
  - Goya: Sazon test C: Mom's Reward, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-046)
  - Goya: Sazon test C: Mom's Reward, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-047)
  - Goya: Sazon test C: Mom's Reward, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-048)
  - Goya: Sazon test: Mom's Reward, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-049)
  - Goya: Sazon test: Mom's Reward, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-050)
  - Goya: Sazon test: Mom's Reward, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-051)
  - Goya: Sazon test: Mom's Reward, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-052)
  - Goya: Sazon test C: Mom's Reward, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-053)
  - Goya: Sazon test: Mom's Reward, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-054)
  - Goya: Sazon test C: Mom's Reward, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-055)
  - Goya: Sazon test C: Mom's Reward, 1987 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-056)
  - Goya: Tango 2 versions, 1988 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-057)
  - Goya: Tango 3 versions, 1988 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-058)
  - Goya: Voice-over auditions, Undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-059)
    Lura Barnes-Howes; Lois Dengrove; Joyce West; Joanie Bakum; Leigh Hamilton; Mary Canavanagh
  - Green Dolmatch, 1975 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-060)
  - History of the American Labor Movement, Dr. Ulrich Schiller, Undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-061)
  - Holly Hobbie 2 takes, "Time Back When"; Side A is "Godfrey Sales Philosophy", 1975 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-062)
  - ILGWU, 1990 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-063)
  - ILGWU An American Christmas, 1983 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-064)
  - ILGWU Beverly Reed, Labor Day USA 3 cuts, Undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-065)
  - ILGWU 669: Desenfrenado (Spanish) "Uncontrolled", 1985 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-066)
  - ILGWU Doris Tolley, Barbees Carmen Sp. Difference, Undated (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-067)
  - ILGWU 665 Easter Parade :60, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-068)
  - ILGWU 665 Easter Parade :60, 1986 (Box AV26, Audio-cassette RL11500-CS-069)